One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
To Russian, With Love
Nico Robin, you insolent little...
Don't you think they were
a little too disadvantaged?
Disadvantaged?
Hey, now... do you really think this is meant to be a fair duel or something?
This is an execution, Nico Robin!
I think you have that backwards.
Commander-san, you no longer need to look over your shoulder.
I'll stay with Rebecca!
Thank you, I'm in your debt.
I was just about to be overwhelmed...
with rage!
Palace Plateau
Third Step
What are you guys doing?!
Have mercy!
W-We're just carrying away the corpse of the fallen! Please let us go!
He's not dead yet!
You're right.
And it might take days before he wakes up again, but we want to look after him!
Please! Have a warrior's mercy!
Please have mercy!
I'm begging you!
Okay, fine! Just go already!
Thank you very much!
Jeez...
The Smile Factory
Oh, Senor!
It got through!
Viola-sama, this is the factory team!
What's going on with Princess Mansherry and Leo's group?
The princess might be going through a horrible ordeal as we speak!
I'm so worried!
I just found out something terrible.
Something terrible?!
Wait a moment.
I'll call Leo now, so stay on the line.
Former Royal Plateau
Leo, can you hear me?
Oh, Viola-sama!
We're on our way up the rampart tower now!
We'll reach the chapel in the palace soon!
Leo, you have to hurry!
Giolla is holding Mansherry, and is forcing her to use her ability!
What? That's awful!
Oh no! Hurry up, Leo!
The Rampart Tower Underneath the Royal Palace
There they are! Dwarfs!
They're coming up!
Fire, fire!
The Stairway to the Royal Palace
Bring the bombs! I'll blow them away along with the stairway!
We'll get there in a super hurry!
Hang on a little bit more, Princess Mansherry!
Listen to me already...
princess of the Dwarfs!
Behind the Chapel, First Floor
The Punishment Room
I can't do it anymore...
The Tontatta Chief's Daughter and Princess of the Tontattans
Mansherry
Let me go back to Green Bit!
I can't help you anymore!
Silence!
Who did you call Boa Hancock?!
I-I never... said anything like...
Don't be such a baby!
It's time to unleash your ability!
Look!
Look at the fallen commanders!
The people who fought against our commanders, however...
They may have been victorious,
but they were gravely injured in their fights.
If you resuscitate the commanders with your Healing Fruit power,
our foes will be powerless, and have to accept their own deaths!
The battle will be completely turned in our favor!
Now,
use the ability that recovered Sugar earlier again!
Take out the watering can filled with magic water!
Now! Now!
Now!
I've learned...
that you're bad people who caused trouble for King Riku...
and that King Doflamingo is lying to us.
So what?! Stop acting so high and mighty, you brazen Tontattan!
I don't want to cure bad people anymore!
So...
So adorable!
Adorable!
Hey, stay focused!
Who did you call the once-in-a-millennium beauty?!
Now!
Help!
Well then...
I take it you don't care what happens to your friends at the factory?
B-But if I heal their wounds, they'll just hurt somebody again, won't they?!
You cheeky little brat!
I'll do whatever it takes to squeeze the power out of you!
Help me, Leo!
I hit one!
Kabu-san!
Kabu-san?! Leo! What happened to him?!
Don't stop!
Go ahead, Leo!
I'll catch up with you soon! I'm okay!
That hurts! You're hurting me!
What happened to me?
His injuries were healed!
I see, princess of the Dwarfs.
I guess you can heal wounds with your tears, too.
Cry some more!
No!
Come on! Shed more healing tears!
It hurts! Help!
Leo, hurry!
Right away!
What's wrong, Viola?!
Giolla noticed Mansherry's tears can heal wounds!
What?!
She's beating her cruelly to make her shed tears!
Princess!
I, Mousey, will come save you now!
It's no use! We have to count on Leo and Kabu-san for now!
The princess of the Tontattas has the power to heal?!
She ate the Healing Fruit.
The basis of its power is healing wounds of living things.
No wonder the enemy wants it.
Indeed.
They're trying to use that power to bring the fallen commanders back to full strength!
If they do, we're done for!
This is super bad!
Leo, we're counting on you!
Kabu-san, hang in there!
But Sugar isn't with them, right?
She is!
Whaaat?!
They're coming back?! You've got to be kidding!
You can do it, Leo!
Go! Take back the princess!
Indeed!
There it is! The punishment room!
I found her!
Leo!
Princess!
You're too late!
Get him!
Now, come back, commanders of the Donquixote Family!
Round Two, begins!
Leo!
Outta my way!
You take care of Giolla!
Beetle...
Uppercut!
What?!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
Sew!
Sew...
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
I'll line them up and try again!
There's no need!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew...
What?!
I'll sew you all up together so you'll never get separated!
What is this?!
Haute Couture!
High Class Sewing
Patchwork!
What?!
Leo came to save me...
He's like a prince!
It... is... art...
Former Royal Plateau
He made it! That was really close!
R-Really?!
He finished off Giolla before she could restore anyone!
Small person, a job well done!
Mansherry has been saved!
Yeah!
Leo, I was scared...
Princess, you gained some weight again.
The Tontattan Princess, Mansherry
Rescued successfully
Same old...
Leo! Leo!
I hurt my leg.
You can carry me on your back if you want!
Or you can carry me in your arms, that works too.
There it is! The Princess' selfishness!
If you really were hurt, you could heal yourself!
You've always been a good runner,
so let's just run and get out of here!
Then I'm not going anywhere.
What?! There it is!
The Princess' entitlement!
It's not like I want your help anyway.
What's with that attitude?!
I really will leave you here!
Fine by me!
Just carry her on your back already!
We gotta go!
Ow...
Honestly!
You're selfish, entitled, and quick-tempered...
You're such a bother, Princess!
Leo's back...
She's nice to everyone besides him.
How dense are you, Leo?
This is awful!
They stole Mansherry away! Catch those Dwarfs!
They went that way! Don't let them get away!
I... I failed...
But this is a crisis!
I have to report this to the young master!
Mansherry's ultimate ability is essential to the young master's plan.
Her ability to restore things
in exchange for shortening her life!
Even if something happens to the Smile factory,
as long as we have the Healing Fruit power on our side,
we can restore it. I'm sure that's what he's thinking!
If nothing is done, th-th...
The factory will be destroyed!
The SMILE Factory
Franky vs. Senor Pink
Senor, defend the factory at all costs!
Franky...
No! Dodge, Senor!
Strong...
Hammer!
Oh! He dove into the ground again!
Fraland, he's gonna do it again!
Dodge!
Meow-Meow...
Suplex!
Oh! Senor!
Neither of them can keep this up!
Fraland!
I know you could have dodged that attack, Fraland!
You've taken that same attack thirty times in a row now! Why?!
Stay out of this, Tontattans.
Yeah... Senor took the same punch thirty times too.
Why is that?!
When somebody offers you a drink at a bar,
if you're a real man, you don't pull your glass away!
What?! Then, don't tell me you were...
This guy is one staunch dude. So I...
will not try to avoid a single attack he throws at me.
I'll take all of his attacks head-on, and still win at the end!
That's my... Strong-style!
I know you're worried, but this is a manly duel!
I'll win no matter what, so just you watch!
I won't let you guys become their slaves again!
Fraland!
You make me drunker than some cheap bar, kid.
Don't forget what you just said!
I'm...
not exactly young anymore.
Let me end it with this next move.
Senor, can I say one thing before that?!
You're far away! Way too far away!
You understand what I'm getting at, right?
You said you'd take all my attacks head-on.
If you want to live up to your manly declaration,
then take this and...
try staying alive!
If, against all odds,
you manage to get back up afterwards, I've lost.
I'll take your final attack head-on!
Fine by me!
He's swimming through the wall of the tower!
What is he up to?!
Unfortunately, the sky isn't particularly friendly today.
Otherwise, if I kept going up,
I'd be able to see Russian.
Russian?
Yeah... I have a son named Gimlet, too.
But unfortunately, gravity persists. I can't keep going up.
Hey! What are you talking about?!
Cyborg, your back is flesh and blood, isn't it?
You... figured that out?!
Now, stop talking!
Or you'll bite your own tongue off!
Meow-Meow Suplex!
Baby...
Buster!
Fraland!
You gave me your word...
so it's my turn now!
I've lost.
Sorry, young master.
Franky...
Iron Boxing!
Oh, right...
Russian...
The day that I met you...
and the day that you stopped smiling...
They were both nights of pouring rain like this...
The rain came out of nowhere, didn't it? I'm soaked!
You're soaking wet, but you're smiling?
I... like rain.
Things that I don't like? Hmm...
Oh, pirates! I hate them to death!
What do you do for a living? C'mon, tell me.
I-I work at a bank.
Really...
Darling!
Well, Darling, what should we name him?
Let's see...
Gimlet.
That's a great name!
What?
Gimlet died?
A week ago today, the day you left without notice,
his temperature went up suddenly...
and I took him to the hospital,
but there was nothing they could do!
Liar...
What?
Liar!
I called the bank several times!
And they said they didn't have anyone like you working for them!
Please! Tell me the truth!
What do you really do for a living?!
What kind of money are we living on?!
Answer me!
Come on! Can't you answer?!
You're not worthy to be a father anymore!
Get out of my way!
W-Wait!
Wait, Russian! It's still stormy outside!
Do you take me for a fool?!
Don't follow me!
It's not what you think, Russian...
The reason I can't tell you everything is...
Russian!
Where are you?!
Because of the rain,
there was a mudslide right above your wife,
and she was caught in it.
Her condition is quite serious.
In a vegetative state?
Yes, she is unconscious.
I'm sorry, but the way things are now,
she'll probably never be able to express her feelings again.
I don't know how long her body can last, either...
If only you hadn't met me, you would've...
Thank you, Darling!
I'm sorry! I didn't wanna lose you...
So I lied!
I want to hear her respond...
I want to hear her voice...
One more time...
Just one more time...
I want her to smile.
One more time...
Russian, look.
I found the same bonnet that Gimlet used to wear!
Well, do I look like him?
He took after me, and all.
I-I'm sorry! I went too far with that joke.
If someone sees me wearing this...
Russian.
You're one hell of a character, old man!
He lost his son, and his wife was in a terrible accident.
That's enough to break anyone.
Pink, what the hell happened to your fashion sense?!
Hey!
I'm going out.
Look! It's a pervert!
Pervert passing through!
Disgusting!
Oh! It's a freak!
Hey! Stop that!
Russian...
To me,
these outfits are more valuable than the finest suits money can buy.
Because the times I wear these outfits...
are the only times you smile for me.
Senor!
Fraland!
Pathetic.
Just what could you be recalling...
that made you cry like that?
Brother.
If we meet again someday, somewhere...
Let's have a drink,
and then you can tell me...
about that woman, Russian.
The battle at the Smile Factory
Winner: Franky